

EMMANUEL RODRÍGUEZ BARAJAS

I am 24 years old, I am a Computer Systems Engineer. I am very interested in video game programming and design, as well as both frontend and back-end web development. Some of my favorite hobbies are playing video games, playing guitar and of course hearing music, I have even started to collect vinyl records. I like to meet new people and I am willing to collaborate with new people on projects related to my interests.

CONTACT INFO

Celphone: +52 473 118 77 37

e-mail: emmanuelrdzbjs@gmail.com

Twitter: @EI_Memex

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/memesinx

EDUCATION

Universidad De Guanajuato

Bachelor in Computer Systems

• January 2017 - June 2022

COURSES

Diploma: Creation And Videogame Development

GameCoder Studios | February 2020 - December 2020

CPA: Programming scentials in C++

Cisco Networking Academy | May 2022 - July 2022

Unreal Engine From 0 Course

Udemy | July 2022 -Present

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native.

English: Advanced

WORK EXPERIENCE

Layout and web development wizard VIMEJI AC | April 2021 - September 2021

- IT department assistant for the optimization of the company's spanish website.
- Creation of an online food warehouse, where workers could manage food deliveries, as well as its distribution.

Online Store Development Mironova Top Studios | February 2022 - June 2022

• Front-end development of the Mironova Top Studios website (online store).

MAIN PROJECTS

SUPER STAR VIOLET

1st person shooter game for PC on itch.io

• Creation of an artificial intelligence for the enemies, as well as their collitions and programming.

LABYRINTH

1st person scaperoom game for PC on itch.io

- Team leader.
- Level Design.
- Main character programming and object interaction

MR. WEENIE'S ODYSSEY

3rd Person Collectaton game for PC made for GMTK GameJam 2020

- Player collitions.
- Prop attachments and joints.
- Main character Interactivity and item collection.

TECHINCAL SKILLS

- C/C++ (4 years).
- Unreal Engine (2 years).
- HTML, CSS and JavaScript. (2 years)
- SQL databases.
- Python, Java.
- Shopify.
- Arduino and Microship procesors programming.